Guide to the Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies records, 1966-2014 RL.11552
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Center Offices, 1969-2013
  - Office of Information Resources (OOR/Library), 1964-2013
    - OOR Subject files, 1972-2013
      - OOR Economics, files, 1972-2009
        - Black Economic Progress, 1988 (Box 139)
        - American Association of Blacks in Energy, 1988-1990 (Box 145)
        - Carson, Emmett D. - Attitudes, Accessibility, and Participation of Blacks and Whites, 1988 May (Box 139)
        - Richard v. Croson, decision, 1989 (Box 154)
        - Bates, Timothy - Major Studies of Minority Business, 1989 Jan (Box 139)
        - Church Support of Individuals and Organizations, 1989 Mar 10-11 (Box 139)
        - Carson, Emmett D. - Contemporary Trends in Black Philanthropy, 1989 Jun 2 (Box 139)
        - Black Philanthropy in America, 1989 Dec 4 (Box 139)
        - Draft Tables for Black Educational Trends, 1989 Sep (Box 139)
        - Allen, Joyce E. - Black Female-Headed Families, 1990 (Box 139)
        - Allen, Joyce - Institutions in a Changing Socio-Economic Environment, 1990 (Box 139)
        - Allen, Joyce E. - Baltimore's Private Sector, 1990-1991 (Box 139)
        - Williams, Rhonda M. - Beyond Bad Luck, 1990 Feb (Box 139)
        - Energy Brain Trust, 1991 (Box 154)
        - Poverty and Social Marginality, 1991 Jan 16-18 (Box 139)
        - Allen, Joyce E. - Job Patterns of Blacks in Metropolitan Areas, 1991 Mar (Box 139)
        - Allen, Joyce E. - Skills Acquisition by Disadvantaged Black Youth, 1991 Apr (Box 139)
        - The Changing Black Family, final report, 1991 May 23 (Box 154)
        - The Changing Black Family, final report, 1991 May 23 (Box 154)
        - Osterman, Paul - Is There a Problem with the Youth Labor Market, 1991 Aug 11 (Box 154)
        - Osterman, Paul - Is There a Problem with the Youth Labor Market, 1991 Aug 11 (Box 154)
        - Beyond Affirmative Action, 1991 Dec 10 (Box 139)
        - Mayer, Susan - A Comparison of Poverty and Living Conditions, 1992 (Box 154)
        - Simms, Margaret C. - Changing Patterns of Family Income, 1992 (Box 139)
        - Scruggs, Yvonne - Then and Now, 1963-1993 (Box 139)
        - Investing in People, 1993 Feb 2 (Box 139)
        - Youth Apprenticeships, 1993 Mar (Box 139)
        - Blacks and Japanese, 1994 (Box 154)
        - Characteristics of housing and neighborhoods by households, 1994 (Box 139)
        - Community Programs that Serve Young Black Males, 1994 Jun 6 (Box 139)
        - Poverty survey summary, 1995 (Box 154)
        - Unheard Voices, 1995 (Box 139)
        - McFate, Katherine - Welfare to Work, 1996 Mar 29 (Box 139)
        - What Devolution Means to the American Public, 1997 (Box 154)
        - One Year After Welfare Reform Implementation, status report, 1997 Nov 12 (Box 139)
        - Allen, Winston J. - Equitable Transportation, 1998 May (Box 139)
        - American Express, 2000 (Box 154)
        - Education and employment, 2000; undated (Box 154)
        - Estimating the Cost of Effective Teen Pregnancy, 2001 Mar (Box 139)
        - New Media and Community Institute Planning Forum, 2008 Feb 25-26 (Box 139)
        - The People's Inaugural Project, 2009 Jan 19-20 (Box 139)
      - OOR Economics, brochures and pamphlets, 1971-2011
        Included are Joint Center materials published by the Joint Center for use by government representatives and the general public, including pamphlets and brochures, that address economic issues and are arranged chronologically.
        - Challenges We Face for Economic Advancement, undated (Box 126)
        - Welfare reform, 1971; 1985; 1995 (Box 126)
        - Distressed communities, revenue sharing, 1973; 2000 (Box 126)
        - Burkhead, Jesse, and Paul Bringewatt - Municipal Budgeting: A Primer for Elected Officials, 1974; 1977 (Box 126)
        - Employment and workforce, 1975; 1982; 2002 (Box 126)
        - Energy and economics, 1978; 1985; 2013 (Box 126)
        - Technical Assistance Resource Guide, 1980 May (Box 126)
        - Meeting Urban Transportation Needs in the 1980s, 1982 Nov 27 (Box 126)
        - Felder, Henry E. - The Changing Patterns of Black Family Income, 1982-1983 (Box 126)
        - Inequity, 1983; 1990-1991 (Box 126)
        - Black economic progress, 1985-1989; 2009-2010 (Box 126)
        - Minority business ownership, 1986; 1989 (Box 126)
        - McFate, Katherine - Crime, Drugs and the Urban Poor, 1989 Nov 17 (Box 126)
        - Rexroat, Cynthia - The Declining Economic Status of Black Children: Examining the Change, 1990; 1994 (Box 126)
        - Workforce training, 1991; 1995; 2005 (Box 126)
        - Affirmative Action, 1995; 1996 (Box 126)
        - Minority business access to capital, 1995; 2001; 2003 (Box 126)
        - Employment trends, 1996; 2000 (Box 126)
        - Welfare reform, 1997; 2006; 2010 (Box 126)
        - Economic trends and issues, 1999; undated (Box 126)
        - Economic prospects, wealth gap, 2000; 2010; undated (Box 126)
        - Yanaka, Hisako - African Americans and Japanese Firms in Georgia, 2001 (Box 126)
        - Neighborhood reinvestment, 2001; 2007 (Box 126)
        - Trader-Leigh, Karyn - Building Cultural Competence: A Tool Kit for Workforce Development, 2002 (Box 126)
        - Trader-Leigh, Karyn - Fresh Start: An On-the-job Survival Guide, 2002 (Box 126)
        - Race and neighborhoods, Katrina, New Orleans, 2008; 2011 (Box 126)
      - OOR Education, files, 1975-2002
        Arranged chronologically and contains materials related to education such as working and published papers, conference materials, meeting transcripts, and lists of school board members.
        - McGuire, Robert G., III, 1975 (Box 146)
        - Dawkins, Marvin P. - Alcoholism Research and Blacks, 1976 Jan 29-31 (Box 146)
        - Orfield, Gary - Desegregation of Black and Hispanic Students, 1982 (Box 146)
        - Orfield, Gary - School Desegregation Patterns, 1983 (Box 146)
        - The Wingspread Journal, 1986 Sep (Box 146)
        - Publications on education, 1986; 1989; 1993 (Box 146)
        - Black school board members, 1987 Jun 5 (Box 146)
        - School Segregation in the 1980s: Trends in the US and Metropolitan Areas, 1987 Jun 5 (Box 146)
        - Black family, 1987-1988 (Box 146)
        - National Caucus of Black School Board Members Annual Conference, 1988 (Box 146)
        - Diversity Within American Schools, 1990 (Box 146)
        - Education Conference on Restructuring America's Public Schools, 1990 May 8-9 (Box 146)
        - Higher education draft essay and meeting transcript, 1991 Jun 4-5; 2 folders (Box 146)
        - Meeting the Challenge of Diversity: School to Work Transition for At-Risk Youth, 1991 Sep (Box 146)
        - Affirmative Action, Inc., 1998 (Box 146)
        - Closing the Digital Divide, 2000 Sep 15 (Box 146)
        - Youth Development Needs and Capabilities, 2002 Mar (Box 146)
      - OOR Education, brochures and pamphlets, 1975-2011
        Publications produced by Joint Center are arranged chronologically and contains pamphlets and brochures for use by government representatives and the general public, that address urban schools, segregation and other education issues.
        - Urban schools, 1975; 1994 (Box 126)
        - Youth Leadership Development Program Handbook, 1980 (Box 126)
        - School segregation, desegregation, 1983; 1985; 1987 (Box 126)
        - Update on Law-Related Education, The Living Constitution, 1988 (Box 126)
        - Public schools, 1989; 1999; 2006 (Box 126)
        - Economic publications, 1990-1995 (Box 126)
        - Education publications, 1991-2011 (Box 126)
        - Higher education, 1993; 2006 (Box 126)
        - Education demographics, 1996; 1999 (Box 126)
      - OOR Health, files, 1972-2012
        Includes materials related to African American health concerns, published and unpublished essays, conference proceedings, studies, and research arranged chronologically.
        - Men's health, undated (Box 154)
        - Children and Lead Poisoning, 1972 Dec (Box 154)
        - A New Comprehensive Training and Technical Assistance Program for Public Officials, 1979-1980 (Box 154)
        - Williams, Eddie N., speeches, 1988 Apr 21-1999 Jul 26 (Box 154)
        - Anti-Drug Abuse Conference, 1990 Oct 22-23 (Box 154)
        - Intergovernmental AIDS Resource, 1990 (Box 154)
        - AIDS, 1990-1991; 2 folders (Box 154)
        - Teenage Pregnancy Among Blacks in the United States, 1991 Feb (Box 154)
        - AT&T Foundation, final report, 1991 May 24 (Box 154)
        - Health Policy Program, 1992 Feb (Box 154)
        - Prescriptions for Change, 1992 Oct 19 (Box 154)
        - Implications of Healthcare Reform Proposals for Black Americans, 1993 Jan 6 (Box 154)
        - The Future of Urban Public Hospitals, 1998 Sep (Box 154)
        - Ethical Issues in the Prevention and Control of Environmentally- Provoked Diseases, 1998 Sep 21-22 (Box 154)
        - Aetna, 1998 (Box 154)
        - Annual report, 1998-2000 (Box 154)
        - Structural racism and reproductive health, funding, 2004-2006; 2 folders (Box 154)
        - Paternal involvement, pregnancy, 2006 (Box 154)
        - Development in progress, 2007-2012 (Box 154)
        - National Center for Health and Behavioral Change, 2010 (Box 154)
        - Health equity, 2012 Jul (Box 154)
        - Men's health assessment, 2012 (Box 154)
        - Paternal involvement, research, 2012 (Box 154)
        - Pregnancy, paternal presence, 2012 (Box 154)
        - Health Policy Institute, conference materials, 2012 (Box 154)
      - OOR Health, brochures and pamphlets, 1972-2007
        Publications produced by Joint Center are arranged chronologically and contains printed materials, including pamphlets and brochures, that address healthcare issues of concern to the African American community for use by government representatives and the general public. The materials did not have a discernible original order and have been arranged chronologically.
        - Drug abuse, 1972; undated (Box 123)
        - Children's health, 1972-2007; 1997-2006; 2 folders (Box 123)
        - African American health, 1984-2012; undated (Box 123)
        - Meeting health needs, 1993-1997; 5 folders (Box 123)
        - Health equity and inequality, 1993-2012; 3 folders (Box 122)
        - Policy, Medicare, Medicaid, 1993-2013; 3 folders (Box 122)
        - Community-based health, 1994-2004; 3 folders (Box 123)
        - Women's health, 1994-2007 (Box 123)
        - African American Health Advocates' Resource Book, 1998 (Box 123)
        - HIV and AIDS, 1999-2010; 2 folders (Box 123)
        - Reproductive health, 2002-2006 (Box 123)
        - Health Policy Institute, 2002-2012 (Box 123)
        - Men's health, 2004-2006 (Box 123)
        - Youth health, 2006-2007; 2 folders (Box 123)
      - OOR Public policy, files, 1969-2011
        Includes published and unpublished essays, conference proceedings, studies, and research related to a broad range of public policy issue, arranged chronologically.
        - Bositis, David A. - Open Society Institute, report, undated (Box 136)
        - Commission on Black Men and Boys, undated (Box 136)
        - Index Federal Civil Rights Enforcement, undated (Box 136)
        - McFate, Katherine - Cocaine and Young Black Males, undated (Box 136)
        - McFate, Katherine - Drug Abuse Among Young Black Males, undated (Box 136)
        - McFate, Katherine - Urban Violence, undated (Box 136)
        - McFate, Katherine, and Cheryl Reed - Drug Offenders, Sentencing, and Alternatives to Incarceration, undated (Box 136)
        - Persian Gulf War, undated (Box 136)
        - Report, undated (Box 136)
        - Research Advisory Council, undated (Box 137)
        - Revenue planning, undated (Box 137)
        - Urban Drug Abuse Project, undated (Box 137)
        - Williams, Eddie N. - Rising to the Level of Self-Criticism, undated (Box 137)
        - Special Projects Community Access Television, 1969 Sep 8-1973 May 24; 3 folders (Box 137)
        - News from Metropolitan Applied Research Center, 1970 Mar 31 (Box 137)
        - Congressional action, 1970 Oct-1981 May (Box 137)
        - Public broadcasting debate, 1972-1980 (Box 137)
        - Conferences, 1972-1990; 2 folders (Box 138)
        - Public Policy Series - Federal Drug Abuse Programs, 1972 Dec (Box 137)
        - Minority Community and Revenue Sharing, 1973 (Box 137)
        - Organizations Concerned with Civil Rights, 1973 Feb 7-1980 Sep 19 (Box 137)
        - Public Policy Series - Regionalism and Minority Participation, 1973 Aug (Box 137)
        - Technical Assistance Centers, 1974; 2 folders (Box 137)
        - Bryce, Herrington J. - Problems of Governing American Cities, 1974 Aug 22 (Box 137)
        - Public Policy Research Program, 1975 Nov 7 (Box 137)
        - Corporate and State Assistance to Local Governments, 1975 Dec (Box 137)
        - Sautter, Carl - Techniques of Coalition-Building, 1975 Dec (Box 137)
        - Consolidated Procedural Rules for Civil Rights Enforcement, 1976 May 3 (Box 137)
        - Conference on Problems of Inner City Food Distribution, 1977 Apr 18-19 (Box 137)
        - Williams, Eddie, articles, 1979 Mar 2-1993 Nov 11 (Box 138)
        - Public Policy Research planning meeting, 1980 Dec 16 (Box 137)
        - Current Issues in U.S. Foreign Relations, 1981 May 14-15 (Box 138)
        - Voting Rights Extension, 1981 Aug 11 (Box 137)
        - Savas, E. S. - Toward a New National Urban Policy, 1981 Sep 21 (Box 137)
        - Committee on Policy for Racial Justice, 1981-1990; 9 folders (Box 137)
        - Orfield, Gary - Desegregation of Black and Hispanic Students, 1982 (Box 137)
        - Blacks, Demographic Change, and Urban Policy, 1982 Jan (Box 137)
        - O'Hare, William P. - On Cutback in the Federal Statistical System, 1982 Mar 16 (Box 137)
        - O'Hare, William P. - Correlates of Recent Black Suburbanization, 1982 Aug 16-19 (Box 137)
        - Blacks, Demographic Change, and Public Policy, 1982 Sep 16-17 (Box 137)
        - Research and Public Policy Institution, 1982 Sep 17 (Box 137)
        - O'Hare, William P. - Recent Black Suburbanization in the South, 1982 Oct 6-8 (Box 138)
        - Orfield, Gary - School Desegregation Patterns, 1983 (Box 138)
        - Black Suburbanization, 1983 Jan (Box 137)
        - Meeting Urban Transportation Needs in the 1980 Workshop, 1983 Jan (Box 137)
        - Williams, Eddie - Structural Discrimination, 1983 Feb 23 (Box 138)
        - O'Hare, William P. - Statistical Policy and Public Policy, 1983 Mar (Box 137)
        - Civil Rights Leadership Conference, 1983 Mar 23; 1 folders (Box 137)
        - Civil Rights Leadership Conference, 1983 Mar 23; 2 folders (Box 138)
        - Project Management Plan, 1983 Jul (Box 138)
        - O'Hare, William - Racial Differences in the Journey to Work, 1983 Aug (Box 138)
        - Industrial Policy and Minority Economic Policy, 1983 Oct 13-14 (Box 138)
        - O'Hare, William P. - A Squeeze on the Federal Statistical System, 1983 Nov 22 (Box 138)
        - Gallup surveys and correspondence, 1984-1989; 5 folders (Box 138)
        - The Civil Rights Act Two Decades Later, 1984 Jun 28-29 (Box 138)
        - Black Women in the Military, roundtable, 1985 Mar 15 (Box 138)
        - Issues of Non-Command Sponsored Families - Korea, 1985 May (Box 138)
        - Dorn, Edwin - Blacks and National Defense, 1985 Jul 22 (Box 138)
        - Racial and Religious Violence, 1985 Sep (Box 138)
        - Racial Inequality, 1940-1980, 1985 Sep 27 (Box 138)
        - Tax Reform and its Special Implications for Blacks, 1985 Dec (Box 138)
        - Welfare Reform, 1985 Dec (Box 138)
        - Ethnocentrism, 1986 (Box 138)
        - Press and the Judicial Protection of Constitutional Liberties, 1986 (Box 138)
        - Richardson, Henry J. III - International Law and Afro-America, 1986 (Box 138)
        - Parker, Frank R. - Legislative Reapportionment in Mississippi, 1986 Feb 7-8 (Box 138)
        - Williams, Eddie N. - St. Louis Policy Framework for Racial Justice Forum, speech, 1986 Jun 1 (Box 138)
        - American Demographics, 1986 Jul (Box 138)
        - Black elderly and aging, 1987 (Box 138)
        - Analysis of Department of Defense Procurement Management Information System, 1987 May 29 (Box 138)
        - After the Zero Option, 1988 (Box 138)
        - U.S.-Japan Project, 1988; 1991 (Box 138)
        - War on Drugs roundtable, 1988 Feb 25 (Box 138)
        - Rexroat, Cynthia - The Changing Black Family, 1988 May 25 (Box 138)
        - Poverty and Public Policy Conference, 1989; 2 folders (Box 138)
        - Turning It Around, screening, 1989 (Box 138)
        - Redistricting in the 1990s, 1989 Jul (Box 138)
        - Poverty and Public Policy, 1989 Dec 4-5 (Box 138)
        - The 1990 Census, 1990 Mar (Box 138)
        - Opportunity Perestroika, 1990 Jun 5 (Box 138)
        - The Urban Anti-Drug Abuse Conference, 1990 Oct 22-23; 3 folders (Box 138)
        - Black Children in Poverty, 1990 Dec 10 (Box 138)
        - Committee on Policy for Racial Justice, 1991 (Box 138)
        - Ford Foundation, continued funding, 1991 May 3 (Box 138)
        - Human rights study group, luncheon, 1991 Aug 16 (Box 138)
        - Emergency Community Development Act of 1992, 1992 Jan 29 (Box 138)
        - Reducing Adolescent Involvement in Drug Trafficking and Violence, 1992 Mar 6-8 (Box 138)
        - McFate, Katherine - Blacks and Crime, 1992 May 12 (Box 138)
        - McFate, Katherine - Black Crime, White Fear, 1992 May 12 (Box 138)
        - Innovations, New Directions, and New Convergences in Poverty Alleviation, 1992 May 21 (Box 138)
        - Urban Policy Institute Program, 1992 Jul (Box 138)
        - Crime, violence, and handguns, 1993 (Box 138)
        - McCloskey Revisited, 1993 Sep 2-5 (Box 138)
        - Board of Governors Retreat, 1993 Sep 30 (Box 138)
        - The Turbulent Friendship, 1993 Nov (Box 138)
        - Chicago UPI Urban Agenda Roundtable, 1994; 2 folders (Box 138)
        - Scruggs, Y. - Counter Costs to the Black Community of Violence, 1994 Jan 7 (Box 138)
        - Wilhelmina, Leigh A. - Housing and Neighborhood Characteristics, 1994 Mar (Box 138)
        - Metropolitan Area Comparisons, 1994 Oct (Box 138)
        - A Proposal to Reduce the Adverse Impact of Television Violence on Children, 1994 Oct (Box 138)
        - The Re(e)Emergence of Hate Groups in the United States Military, 1996 (Box 138)
        - Bositis, David A. - Second Circuit Taskforce, 1997 Jan 31 (Box 138)
        - Board of Governors meeting, 1997 Sep 3; 1998 Jul 8; 2 folders (Box 138)
        - Meeting the Need for Information, 1998 Apr (Box 138)
        - Board of Governors Research Committee meeting, 1998 Jul 8 (Box 138)
        - Development Committee meeting, 1998 Jul 8 (Box 138)
        - Sigma Pi Phi's Report and Recommendations of the Public Policy Committee, 1998-2000 (Box 138)
        - Bositis, David A. - Black Churches in the Faith Based Initiative, 2006 Sep (Box 138)
        - Improving the Lives of African Americans and Other Communities of Color, 2008 Mar (Box 138)
        - A Lost Decade, 2011 Sep (Box 138)
      - OOR Public policy, brochures and pamphlets, 1972-2013
        This subseries contains printed materials addressing policy issues that were produced by the Joint Center and include pamphlets and brochures for use by government representatives and the general public .These materials did not have a discernible original order and have been arranged chronologically by topic.
        - A New Approach to Local Problem Solving, undated (Box 118)
        - Local and metropolitan government, 1972; 1978-1987 (Box 118)
        - Nelson, William E., Jr. - Black Politics in Gary, 1972 Mar (Box 118)
        - Dean, John - The Making of a Black Mayor, 1973 (Box 118)
        - Morris, Milton D. - New Federalism and Community Development, 1976 Jun (Box 118)
        - Environmental policy, 1977-2012; 2 folders (Box 118)
        - Energy and Equity: Some Social Concerns, 1978; Jun 27 (Box 122)
        - Managing Scarce Resources, 1978 Nov 17-19 (Box 122)
        - Community programs, 1980; 1994; 2001 (Box 120)
        - Foreign Trade Policy and Black Economic Advancement, 1980 May 15 (Box 118)
        - Black Americans and the Shaping of U.S. Foreign Policy, 1980 May 22 (Box 118)
        - Clark, Kenneth Bancroft, and John Hope Franklin - The Nineteen Eighties, 1981 (Box 118)
        - Humberger, Edward - Urban Policy and the Reagan Revolution, 1981 (Box 118)
        - Public policy, 1981; 1991-1997 (Box 122)
        - Williams, Eddie N. - Public Policy in the Eighties, 1981 Mar 3 (Box 118)
        - A Policy Framework for Racial Justice, 1983 (Box 118)
        - Eisinger, Peter K. - Black Employment in City Government, 1973-1980, 1983 (Box 118)
        - Orfield, Gary - School Desegregation Patterns in the States, Large Cities and Metropolitan Areas, 1968-1980, 1983 (Box 118)
        - Industrial Policy and Minority Economic Opportunity, 1983 Oct (Box 118)
        - Congress and the Constitution, 1984-1988 (Box 120)
        - McGahey, Richard, and John Jeffries - Minorities and the Labor Market, 1985 (Box 118)
        - Elected and Appointed Black Judges in the United States 1986 (Box 118)
        - Poverty and inequality, 1986; 1994; undated (Box 118)
        - Broh, C. Anthony - A Horse of a Different Color, 1987 (Box 118)
        - Christian, Charles M. - Dimensions of Social, Economic, and Geographic Change and their Implications for Black Politics, 1987 (Box 118)
        - Global policy, 1988-1991 (Box 122)
        - McFate, Katherine - The Metropolitan Area Fact Book, 1988 (Box 118)
        - Pettigrew, Thomas F., and Denise A. Alston - Tom Bradley's Campaigns for Governor, 1988 (Box 118)
        - The U.S.-Japan Project, 1988 Aug (Box 118)
        - Considering Japan, 1991 (Box 118)
        - Elected and Appointed Black Judges in the United States 1991 (Box 118)
        - Perceptions vs. Reality, 1991 (Box 118)
        - Williams, Eddie N. - Strategies for Success in the '90s, 1991 Jun 20 (Box 118)
        - Williams, Eddie N. - Building Bridges to the Future, 1991 Oct 26 (Box 118)
        - Williams, Eddie N. - Black-Jewish Relations in the United States, 1991 Nov 12 (Box 118)
        - American and Japanese Communication Styles, 1992 (Box 118)
        - Bositis, David - Black State Legislators, 1992 (Box 118)
        - Reconcilable Differences, 1992 (Box 118)
        - Williams, Eddie N. - The Mechanics of Pluralism: Reflections on the U.S. Experience, 1992 Nov 11 (Box 118)
        - New Directions, 1993 (Box 118)
        - Carson, Emmett D. - A Hand Up, 1993 (Box 118)
        - Williams, Eddie N. - Inclusive Problem-Solving, 1993 May 5 (Box 118)
        - Jordan, Vernon E., Jr. - The Clinton Foreign Policy, 1993 Sep 8 (Box 118)
        - Young Black Males in Jeopardy, 1994 (Box 118)
        - Welfare, 1994-2007 (Box 118)
        - Black Initiative and Governmental Responsibility, 1995 (Box 118)
        - Affirmative Action, 1996 Aug (Box 118)
        - Social Security, 1997-2005 (Box 118)
        - People of color in the military, 1998-2000 (Box 118)
        - Bositis, David A. - Diverging Generations, 2001 (Box 118)
        - Structural racism, 2001-2004 (Box 118)
        - Scarboro Community Assessment Report, 2001 Aug (Box 118)
        - Potapchuk, Maggie - Holding up the Mirror, 2002 (Box 118)
        - Potapchuk, Maggie - Cultivating Independence, 2004 (Box 118)
        - Blacks and the 2004 Republican National Convention (Box 118)
        - Entman, Robert M. - Young Men of Color in the Media, 2005 Nov 30 (Box 118)
        - A Way Out, 2006 (Box 118)
        - Cahn, Edgar S. - How the Juvenile Justice System Reduces Life Options of Minority Youth, 2006 (Box 118)